Thank you for watching!
You guys aren't in there.
There you go.
Goal.
Oh, my God.
It's open.
It's still open.
Oh, my God.
It's in.
I'm serious. I'm serious.
It's not in.
Yes, it was.
It's done.
It's over.
Don't interrupt me. What?
No, I'm not going in with you guys at all.
I'm sure this will give you confidence that you're in.
Right here, right here.
Isn't that right?
The soundboard is over there.
No, it wasn't in there.
It's not too sweet.
It's not sweet enough?
I don't know, I'm getting blamed.
We're looking at the ocean.
Can I get a little sugar? I really do.
Spoiled. It's a compromise.
It's a compromise.
I'm going to end my commentary here this time.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you next time.
Bye-bye!
me
me me
Yeah, we only have to do it once.
Let's all get in here and foe it.
You can afford it.
You've got the diehards here.
There's plenty of room here, right?
Here we go.
Oh, it's so close.
So close.
I'll go one more time.
Here I go.
You're so good.
Yay.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
What's that? Huh? Huh? Huh?
That's it for today's Amechare.
Everyone is probably in, so that's a confidence booster.
Well, well, well, well... I'm just going to let you guys think about running away from the real thing, and then we'll take it out of there.
It's perfect.
Please pull it out.
Then, I wonder if we really got even one pitch in. Enjoy it, everyone.
Keep your eyes peeled. So, after this.
Ibaraki Robot's Calf Time Show will also do its best!
Let's have fun together until the end!
Fear me, you belong to me
Tell me why
Thank you for your hard work!
Are you all having fun?
I'd like to do some quick words now.
Let's have fun together!
First of all, let's go!
First of all, when is the first step?
I know it's hard to be brave. It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Free Throw Challenge!
Yeah!
One more!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Let's get some good voices in here!
One more time!
Go, go, go, go!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Come on, come on!
One more step!
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go!
Congratulations.
Did you get three?
I only got one.
Me too.
We didn't put anything in.
It's fun.
I'm done.
I was super nervous.
Super nervous.
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
High time show is over!
That was fun, wasn't it?
Hey.
I was able to put in a lot of work.
But...
Let's start with the ones who got in.
I was let in.
You were let in.
Okay, let's go this way.
Let's see...
How about you two?
From the beginning.
I'm nervous.
We were the first group over here.
I'm the strong one.
You know...
The first two.
You want the first half?
We needed them.
They were the ones throwing the ball the whole time.
Maybe it was for the best.
I don't know.
I'm down. I'm down. I'm down. I'm down. I'm down.
He's got a big grin on his face.
You two... well, I don't care if you're good at sports or not.
I told Mr. Suzuki to come this way.
Which way did you go?
Catch-22.
I changed it. But you couldn't?
No, not for a couple of people.
I couldn't get in.
Can I ask you to apologize to Salam Dunk or Hanamichi?
Why?
For the pose at the end.
This pose?
Can I have him apologize?
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, God, no.
I felt a little embarrassed by that.
I just want to feel like I'm not going to do it.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Thank you! I'm so sorry!
And that's it for this edition of Amechare.
Thank you so much for watching until the end!
It was a lot of fun!